mbuzzy.com 2007-08-22

# mbuzzy.com - images, ringtones, applications for your phone

### mbuzzy Privacy Policy

**Policies**  
A Note to Children and Parents: We intend the mbuzzy web site for use by adults. Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.

**Your Privacy**  
At mbuzzy, we recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you wish to understand what we may do with that information. That's why we have put a policy in place to disclose to you how your personal information may be used. You may visit our web site and browse without giving us any personally identifying information, however certain functions on the web site (such as sending content to your mobile device) and certain areas of the site requiring login may require giving us information (for example, username, password, name, mobile number, and the like). Please read on for more details about our privacy practices.

**What information does mbuzzy collect? How do we use it?**

·  At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information. Generally this information is requested when you use an online service or when you provide information in connection with a transaction.

·  When you request that content be delivered to your mobile device, we ask you for your mobile number. 

·  mbuzzy.com and its service providers may use your personal information to operate our web site and/or effect your transactions, and to create and share reports about your transactions among themselves. 

·  We may automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve you and our customers generally. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, what kind of mobile device you are using, information relating to your geographical region, and your IP address.  
·  We may report to our data providers certain user information, such as items purchased, device types, and the like; however we will not disclose any personally identifiable information when making such reports.   
·  If you establish a credit account with mbuzzy to pay the fees we charge, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date and related tracking information.

**How does mbuzzy protect consumer information?**  
We take reasonable steps to protect the customer data we collect from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Due to the existing regulatory and legal environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, we may need to disclose information in order to stop illegal activity, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our site. 

**What about "cookies"?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies enable us to provide you with more personal service. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that if you would rather not store the information for future use. However, you may not be able to use advanced features of the site, including logging in to your account and purchasing items, without cookies enabled.

**Will mbuzzy disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
mbuzzy may store and disclose personal information as allowed or required by applicable law, including making disclosures that are necessary or advisable to: (a) protect the rights, safety or property of users of our web site, the public, or mbuzzy or our web site suppliers; and (b) conform to legal or regulatory requirements.

If you choose to purchase an item on the mbuzzy Service or open a credit account, use credit/debit card information, bank account direct debit, or otherwise provide us with your financial information, we use your address and billing information to bill you and provide associated support.

mbuzzy will not trade, sell or rent your personal information. mbuzzy may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information.

**Your Consent**  
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by mbuzzy. If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes on this page. Please check this page for changes from time to time to make sure you are aware of our latest privacy practices.  
For those of you visiting us from the European Economic Area, please note that the personal data you enter will be transferred outside the European Economic Area for use by mbuzzy and its service providers for any of the purposes described above. By using our web site and providing us with your personal data, you consent to this transfer of your personal data.

(updated February 16, 2004)
